hi folks so it's Matt again and we are
大家好，再次是Matt，我们是
now going to talk a little bit about
现在要谈一点
solving extensive forum games with
解决与广泛的论坛游戏
incomplete information and moving a
不完整的信息和移动
little bit beyond sub game perfection
超越子游戏的完美点滴
and this is just to give you some
这只是给你一些
impression of stuff that's out there in
里面有东西的印象
game theory we're not going to spend too
博弈论，我们也不会花费
much time on this but I'll give you a
很多时间，但我会给你一个
flavor of it and you know the idea of
它的味道，你知道的想法
solving these kinds of games with is
解决这些游戏是
that it makes things difficult is no sub
它使事情变得困难不是没有子
game perfection and backward induction
游戏完美与向后归纳
had a lot of bite in games with complete
完全喜欢游戏
information because we could analyze
信息，因为我们可以分析
parts of the tree there were a lot of
树的一部分有很多
sub games figure out what's going on in
子游戏找出正在发生的事情
that and that would tell us then we
那，那会告诉我们，然后我们
could simplify that and that gives us an
可以简化这一点，这给了我们一个
idea of what's going to happen other
其他会发生什么的想法
parts of the game with incomplete
游戏中不完整的部分
information there's no proper sub game
信息，没有适当的子游戏
so players don't really know exactly
所以玩家并不十分清楚
which node they're at in a game and that
他们在游戏中位于哪个节点，以及
can be difficult so there may not be
可能很难，所以可能没有
many proper sub games so the the basic
许多适当的子游戏，所以基本
reasoning doesn't apply sub game
推理不适用于子游戏
perfection does not apply directly in a
完美并不直接适用于
lot of games doesn't have much bite but
很多游戏咬的不多，但是
there are ways of extending the
有一些方法可以扩展
reasoning so there are ways to take the
推理，所以有办法采取
same kind of credibility ideas that were
与以前一样的信誉理念
behind sub game perfection and apply
完善子游戏并申请
them in these kinds of games so we'll
他们在这类游戏中，所以我们将
just take a peek at that and just give
偷看一下就给
you a taste of it but we're not going to
您尝一尝，但我们不会
go into it in too much depth ok so let's
深入其中，好吧，让我们
look at a simple game and this game is
看一个简单的游戏，这个游戏是
one where it's an entry decision by one
一个由一个人决定的进入
say one firm player one so they have a
说一个坚定的球员，所以他们有一个
decision of either E or n so think of E
E或n的决定，所以想想E
as enter n is not and player 2 as
因为输入n不是，而玩家2为
another firm say in a market so they're
另一家公司在市场上说，所以他们
already in a marketplace selling a
已经在市场上出售
particular good and from one's deciding
特别好的，由个人决定
should I enter into this market and
我应该进入这个市场并且
compete with the other firm okay so I've
与其他公司竞争好吧，所以我已经
offered it you know there's a coffee
提供它，你知道那里有咖啡
shop open on a particular corner there's
在特定角落开的商店
somebody else thinking okay should I
有人认为我应该
enter right across the street and have a
进入马路对面，有一个
competing coffee shop so from one is now
竞争的咖啡店，所以从现在开始
thinking about entering from
考虑从
- is already there and the question is
-已经在那里，问题是
what happens once they affirm one
他们确认一个后会发生什么
entered so if in terms of payoffs here
在这里输入，因此就收益而言
if firm 1 does not enter if this player
如果公司1没有进入，如果这个玩家
does not enter player 1 gets 0 and
不进入玩家1得到0并且
player 2 ends up getting 2 so the payoff
玩家2最终得到2，所以收益
for player 2 here is 2 if firm 1 does
对于玩家2，如果公司1这样做，则此处为2
not enter and that's that's true either
不输入，那是真的
way it happens if firm 1 doesn't enter
如果公司1没有进入，它将如何发生
and then if firm 1 enters then the
然后如果公司1进入
payoffs depend on whether the the
收益取决于
incumbent coffeeshops a is 1 that's
现有咖啡店的a是1
going to fight so f stands for fight or
要去战斗，所以代表战斗或
a for acquiesce so basically they can
一个默认的，所以基本上他们可以
either say ok look live and let live
要么说好看活着，要么活着
we'll have to coffeeshops we lose some
我们不得不去咖啡店，我们损失了一些
of our business or we can go toe to toe
我们的业务，或者我们可以从头到脚
by offering special coupons discounts
通过提供特别优惠券折扣
we're going to make this miserable for
我们将使这个痛苦
the other for the other company and so
另一个给其他公司等等
the payoffs actually depend on whether
收益实际上取决于
firm 2 fights or not and moreover the
厂商2是否打架，而且
the incomplete information here is about
这里不完整的信息是关于
the strength how good player 1 is so
玩家1的实力如何
they could be a strong player
他们可以成为一个强大的球员
probability 1/2 or they could be a weak
1/2的概率，否则可能会很弱
player so the note up here is a move by
玩家，所以这里的音符是由
nature so nature moves first randomly
自然，所以自然首先会随机移动
picks whether player 1 is strong or not
选择玩家1是否强壮
strong or weak so with probability 1/2
强或弱，所以概率为1/2
they pick a strong player with
他们选择了一个强大的球员
probability 1/2 they pick a weak player
他们选择弱者的概率为1/2
and player 1 gets to see the outcome of
玩家1会看到
that so player 1 this new coffee shop I
玩家1这家新的咖啡店
know whether I've got really good coffee
知道我是否真的有好咖啡
or not player 2 doesn't know what the
还是玩家2不知道
quality of firm 1 is when firm 1 enters
公司1的质量是公司1进入的时间
so a firm 1 is a strong one or from one
因此，企业1是强者或来自强者
is the weak one player 2 cannot
是一名弱者2不能
distinguish between those two different
区分这两个不同
situations and that's why we have these
情况，这就是为什么我们有这些
informations that connected here ok so
在这里连接的信息还可以
that's the structure of the game and
这就是游戏的结构，
basically where is the strong and weak
基本上强者和弱者在哪里
manifest itself in terms of payoffs it
体现自己的回报
manifests itself in terms of
表现为
is what happens if firm 2 fights so firm
如果公司2打得这么坚定，会发生什么
2 fights a strong firm 1 they both get
2打强公司1他们俩都得到
-1 so they both lose if firm 1 is strong
-1，所以如果公司1强大，他们都会输
from 2 fights that's going to be costly
来自2场战斗，这将是昂贵的
for both of them if firm or firm 2
对于他们两个，如果是坚定的或坚定的2
fights a weak entrant then from 2 gets 0
与弱者竞争，然后从2变为0
and from one gets -2 so weakness means
而从一得到-2，所以弱点意味着
that they're do less well in fighting we
他们在对抗我们方面表现不佳
can also in this particular game have a
也可以在这个特定的游戏中
situation here where where the firm 1
这里的情况在哪里坚定1
the weak version of firm 1 even if if
即使公司1的弱版本
firm 2 is accommodating is eventually
商号2最终容纳
going to go out of business they're just
即将倒闭，他们只是
that you know they've got really lousy
你知道他们真的很烂
coffee they're not going to make it okay
咖啡，他们不会让它好起来的
so let's try and analyze this game using
因此，我们尝试使用
sub game perfect well with sub game
子游戏与子游戏完美搭配
perfection there's actually many
完美有很多
equilibria of this game and part of the
此游戏的平衡和部分
problem is that when we're trying to
问题是当我们试图
look at sub games
看子游戏
we can't just chop off this part and say
我们不能只砍掉这部分然后说
it's a sub game because it's not this
这是一个子游戏，因为不是
node is connected to this node for
节点连接到该节点
player 2 they're not sure whether
玩家2他们不确定是否
they're over here or over here so we
他们在这里或这里，所以我们
can't chop off this small pieces and
不能砍掉这小块，
essentially the only sub game is the
本质上唯一的子游戏是
whole game so the only sub game in this
整个游戏，所以这是唯一的子游戏
game is the whole game and so sub game
游戏是整个游戏，所以子游戏
perfection is just the same as Nash
完美与纳什相同
equilibrium in this game so if we're
在这个游戏中保持平衡，所以如果我们
looking at Nash equilibria let's look
看着纳什均衡让我们看看
for a couple of them let's take a peek
对于其中的一些，让我们来看看
at one where firm 1 does not enter right
在公司1没有进入右边的地方
so no matter what firm 1 does not enter
所以无论哪个公司1都不进入
whether they're strong or weak and firm
他们强弱还是坚定
2 plans on fighting ok so firm 2 says
2战斗的计划好那么坚定2说
I'm going to fight you if you enter and
如果你进入我会和你战斗
from 1 says oh that's bad I'm going to
从1开始说哦，那很糟糕，我要
get negative payoffs therefore they
得到负收益，因此他们
don't enter okay so that's one Nash
输入不好，那是纳什之一
equilibrium a Nash equilibrium is one if
如果，纳什均衡为1
they're strong they don't enter if
他们很坚强，如果
they're weak they don't enter and from 2
他们很弱，他们没有进入，从2
only has one information set and if they
只有一个信息集，如果他们
fight right so that's a Nash equilibrium
争取正确，那是纳什均衡
ok it's also sub game perfection given
好吧，这也是子游戏的完美
its sub game there's no
它的子游戏没有
sub-game in this what's strange about
子游戏这有什么奇怪的
that equilibrium what's strange about
那个平衡有什么奇怪的
that equilibrium is if you look at the
那个平衡就是，如果你看
fight decision of player two the fight
选手二的战斗决定
decision is essentially a dominated
决定本质上是决定性的
strategy in the sense that it gives
从某种意义上讲，策略
minus one if the player is strong
如果玩家强壮，则减一
compared to one if they were acquiescing
相比之下，如果他们是默认的
and zero if it's against a weak whereas
如果是弱者则为零，而
one if they acquiesced so no matter what
如果他们默认，那么无论如何
the type of the the firm play two should
公司打两个的类型应该
really equius right they get a higher
真正平等，他们得到了更高
payoff from that so this is somehow not
从中得到回报，所以这不知何故
credible so we're losing credibility but
可信，所以我们正在失去可信度，但是
it's it's still consistent with Nash if
如果它仍然与纳什保持一致
player one really believes firm 2 is
玩家一真的相信公司2是
going to fight and that's fine and if
去打架，那很好，如果
player 1 really never enters well player
玩家1确实从不进入好玩家
2 can say they're going to fight and
2可以说他们要战斗，
they never have to so that following
他们永远不必这样
that strategy doesn't hurt them in a
这种策略不会在一个
sense that they're going to get the two
感觉他们会得到两个
no matter what and so they don't need to
不管是什么，所以他们不需要
deviate away from F if they're never
如果他们永远不会偏离F
called on to move ok so that's that's a
呼吁移动确定，所以那是一个
Nash but the the what if here the off
纳什，但如果在这里怎么办
the equilibrium path behavior of player
玩家的均衡路径行为
two claiming they're going to fight is
两个声称他们要战斗的是
not really credible in this game so um
在这个游戏中不太可靠
what if firm 2 was going to acquiesce
如果公司2要默认怎么办
right so there's another strategy where
对，所以还有另一种策略
we're for two for two we imagine them
我们两个人两个，我们想象他们
acquiescing so what should one do well
默许，所以一个人应该做得好
if one then is strong they should enter
如果有人那么强，他们应该进入
they get a payoff of 1 here 0 if they
如果他们在这里得到1的回报0
don't if they're weak what should they
如果他们很弱就不要
do if they're weak well they shouldn't
如果他们软弱无能，那就不应该这样做
enter right because they get a minus 1
输入正确，因为他们得到负1
here is 0 here so we should not enter ok
这里是0，所以我们不应该输入ok
this is another Nash equilibrium
这是另一个纳什均衡
and in some sense it's a more credible
从某种意义上讲，这是更可信的
Nash equilibrium because in this
纳什均衡，因为在此
situation firm 2 is called on 2 to move
情况公司2被要求2移动
they're actually doing a best response
他们实际上在做出最好的反应
so they're following a best responsive
因此他们正在采取最佳的回应
acquiescing and firm 1 is doing the best
默许和坚定1做到最好
it can if it's strong it's entering if
如果它很强就可以进入
it's weak it's not and this whole thing
它很弱，不是，这整个事情
hangs together as another Nash
挂在一起作为另一个纳什
equilibrium so here there's a couple of
平衡，所以这里有几个
Nash equilibria there's actually more
纳什均衡实际上还有更多
where you have firm 2 doing some mixing
你在公司2做一些混音的地方
and then firm 1 staying out in some
然后公司1留在一些
circumstances and not in others it
情况而不是其他情况
depends on the particular mixtures you
取决于您的特定混合物
work out so there's actually a lot of
算出来，所以实际上有很多
Nash equilibria to this game and so when
纳什均衡到这场比赛，所以什么时候
we when we want to analyze this sub-game
我们当我们想分析这个子游戏时
perfection corresponds with Nash it
完美与纳什相对应
doesn't give us much bite in terms of
并没有给我们很大的帮助
picking out one or another but one idea
挑选一个或另一个但一个主意
behind doing this and analyzing these
这样做并分析这些背后
games is to try and build in the idea
游戏是要尝试建立想法
behind sub liam confection in terms of
在亚利亚甜品后面
sequential rationality and so there are
顺序合理性等
equilibrium concepts that explicitly
明确的均衡概念
model players beliefs about where they
模型玩家对他们在哪里的信念
are in a tree for every information set
对于每个信息集都在树上
and there's two solution concepts in
在其中有两个解决方案概念
particular known as sequential
特别称为顺序
equilibrium and perfect Bayesian
平衡和完美贝叶斯
equilibrium that have key features where
具有关键特征的均衡
they have players as part of the
他们有球员作为
equilibrium you specify what the beliefs
平衡你指定什么信念
of the players are and it should be that
的球员是，应该是
the beliefs are not contradicted by the
信念与
actual play of the game and players best
游戏的实际玩法和玩家最佳
respond to those beliefs so you have
回应这些信念，所以你有
best respondent and and so forth but you
最佳答复者，依此类推，但是您
also make a requirement that the police
还要求警察
aren't contradicted by the actual play
与实际玩法并不矛盾
of a game and players have to best
游戏中，玩家必须做到最好
respond to their beliefs even off the
即使在
equilibrium path and that's going to
平衡路径，这将
have bite in this game so if we look at
咬了这个游戏，所以如果我们看看
this game again and we require that
再次玩这个游戏，我们要求
players have beliefs at different
玩家对不同的信念
information sets so here what we would
信息集，所以在这里我们会
have to have is now player two has to
现在必须拥有的是第二个玩家
say what's the probability that I'm here
说我在这里的几率
what's the probability that I'm here so
我在这里的概率是多少
they have some beliefs but notice in
他们有一些信仰，但注意
this game no matter what those beliefs
这个游戏不管那些信念
are they should always acquiesce right
他们应该总是默许吗
so once we give player two beliefs here
所以一旦我们给玩家两种信念
and say they have to best respond to
说他们必须最好地回应
their beliefs in in any any node where
他们对任何节点的信仰
they have beliefs then that ties down
他们有信念，然后联系在一起
and says okay it player two has to
并说第二个玩家必须
equius then for player one if player two
如果玩家2，则等于玩家1
is a quiescing player one is strong they
是一个安静的球员，他们很强大
should definitely enter if player two is
如果玩家2是
weak they should definitely not enter so
弱者绝对不应该这样进入
we end up with a unique prediction in
我们最终得到了一个独特的预测
this game
这个游戏
whereas with sub game perfection there
而随着子游戏的完善
were many so the idea here is we have
有很多，所以这里的想法是
these extra impositions that players
这些额外的强加给玩家
have beliefs first of all they're not
首先有信念他们不是
contradicted so it has to be that what
矛盾的，所以必须是什么
they're believing is consistent with the
他们认为与
way that other players are playing and
其他玩家的游戏方式
players should best respond to their
玩家最好对他们的反应
beliefs which is imposing credibility at
信念强加于
every information set in the game okay
游戏中设置的所有信息都可以
so this makes it you know ends up making
所以这让你知道最终
a lot of predictions in these kinds of
这些类型的很多预测
games and the date you know the
游戏和您知道的日期
challenges here we see with incomplete
我们在这里看到的挑战并不完整
information there may not be proper sub
信息可能没有正确的子
games the ideas of sequential
游戏顺序的想法
rationality can be extended but they
理性可以扩展，但是他们
require extra layers of solution
需要额外的解决方案
concepts and you know once we do this
概念，一旦执行此操作，您就会知道
we're also layering on a lot more than
我们还不仅仅局限于
we had before and we've seen sub game
我们以前有过，我们看过子游戏
perfection already can be quite
完美已经可以相当
demanding of players here now they also
现在这里的球员要求很高
have to be very good at inferring things
必须非常善于推断事物
based on where they are but when you
根据他们在哪里，但是当你
begin to see things like professional
开始看到像专业的东西
poker players playing they're very much
玩扑克的人很多
going through these kinds of
经历这些
calculations so if another player raised
计算，所以如果另一个玩家加注
a bet what does that mean about what
打赌这意味着什么
their hand is likely to be should I be
他们的手很可能是我
you know what should I do under
你知道我该怎么办
different circumstances if I have a
如果我有一个不同的情况
strong hand should I call should I raise
我应该加注吗？
there and and so forth so what's going
那里等等，这是怎么回事
on in this kinds of solution concepts
在这种解决方案概念中
nonetheless are
尽管如此
are very well-suited to analyzing
非常适合分析
specific kinds of games so there's a lot
特定类型的游戏，所以有很多
more to study even beyond the scope of
甚至超出了研究范围
this course but these are fascinating
这门课，但是这些很有趣
games to begin to wrap your head around
游戏开始缠住你的头